export default [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "0+1?",
    answer: 1,
    answers: {
      a: 1,
      b: 2,
      c: 3,
      d: 4,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "0+2?",
    answer: 2,
    answers: {
      a: 1,
      b: 2,
      c: 3,
      d: 4,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "0+3?",
    answer: 3,
    answers: {
      a: 1,
      b: 2,
      c: 3,
      d: 4,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "0+4?",
    answer: 4,
    answers: {
      a: 1,
      b: 2,
      c: 3,
      d: 4,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "0+5?",
    answer: 5,
    answers: {
      a: 5,
      b: 6,
      c: 7,
      d: 8,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "0+6?",
    answer: 6,
    answers: {
      a: 5,
      b: 6,
      c: 7,
      d: 8,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "0+7?",
    answer: 7,
    answers: {
      a: 5,
      b: 6,
      c: 7,
      d: 8,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "0+8?",
    answer: 8,
    answers: {
      a: 5,
      b: 6,
      c: 7,
      d: 8,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "0+9?",
    answer: 9,
    answers: {
      a: 9,
      b: 10,
      c: 11,
      d: 12,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "0+10?",
    answer: 10,
    answers: {
      a: 9,
      b: 10,
      c: 11,
      d: 12,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "0+11?",
    answer: 11,
    answers: {
      a: 9,
      b: 10,
      c: 11,
      d: 12,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "0+12?",
    answer: 12,
    answers: {
      a: 9,
      b: 10,
      c: 11,
      d: 12,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "0+13?",
    answer: 13,
    answers: {
      a: 13,
      b: 14,
      c: 15,
      d: 16,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "0+14?",
    answer: 14,
    answers: {
      a: 13,
      b: 14,
      c: 15,
      d: 16,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "0+15?",
    answer: 15,
    answers: {
      a: 13,
      b: 14,
      c: 15,
      d: 16,
    },
  },
];
